and on Monday I
y el lunes me
woke up with a really sore throat and
desperté muy mal de la garganta y aun
even with that I went to
esas aun con esas me fui
record that video of the
a a grabar el vídeo ese de la de los
Latin gramis in Seville and
Latin gramis por Sevilla y
all that. You saw the video, a lot of people haven't
demás lo visteis el vídeo mucha gente no
seen it, let's
lo ha visto vamos a
watch it, let's watch it, there are a lot of people who have
verlo vamos a verlo hay mucha gente que
n't seen the video,
no lo vio el vídeo
eh, I do
eh
n't know if I got it right, not the thumbnail and
no sé si fue acertada no la miniatura y
[Music]
[Música]
the the thumbnail and the no, well it has
la la miniatura y la no bueno tiene
13,000 views But the truth is that for
13000 visitas Pero la verdad es que para
the video that should have more, I don't know if I'll
el vídeo que debería tener más no sé si
upload it again with another one, with another
lo volveré a subir con otra con otra
thumbnail and with another title. Maybe,
miniatura y con otro título A lo mejor
eh, a very nice video that's been left
eh un vídeo muy guapo que se ha quedado
a little there,
un poquillo ahí
eh. Let's see, Seville, basically right now
eh A ver Sevilla básicamente ahora mismo
you're walking through Seville and it's
tú vas andando por Sevilla y Está todo
full of police and cars and limousines
lleno de policía y de coches y limusinas
with tinted windows, okay, you're
con los cristales tintados vale tú vas
walking through Seville And you'll probably
andando por Sevilla Y seguramente te
run into Maluma and you don't notice, but of
cruzas con Maluma y no te enteras peres
course they're all these old vans,
claro son todos furgonetas de estas
these old cars, not a van,
vitos coches de estos vitos no furgoneta
eh, black with super
eh negro con con los cristales super
black tinted windows and then you don't
tintados en negro y entonces pues no
know who you're running into, the
sabes con quién te estás cruzando lo
same thing  it's Shakira maybe it's Chayan
mismo es Shakira que lo mismo es chayan
maybe it's you don't know Okay
que lo mismo es no lo sabes Vale
so what was I doing
entonces qué es lo que estaba haciendo
while I was without a voice gossiping
mientras que he estado sin voz cotillear
everywhere a kiss
por todas partes un beso
sisuka a kiss gorgeous Thank you so much
sisuka un beso guapísima Muchísimas
for those 10 members
gracias por esos 10 miembros todo el
everyone in the chat applauding sisuka
mundo en el chat aplaudiendo a sisuka
okay eh
vale
Well here apart from the video that we
eh Bueno aquí aparte del vídeo que hemos
made This video I recorded on Monday
hecho Este vídeo lo grabé el lunes
okay there are a lot of people that I've seen
vale hay mucha gente a la que he visto
that I haven't been able to take pictures of or
que no he podido hacerle fotos ni
ask for pictures or anything like that okay on
pedirle fotos ni nada por el estilo vale
Tuesday Tuesday I went with Lorena
martes el martes me fui con Lorena
because I couldn't work I mean I don't have
porque no podía trabajar o sea no tengo
bz I can't work so
bz no puedo trabajar entonces
eh I left the kids with the grandparents
eh dejé a los niños con con los abuelos
we went for a walk
nos fuimos a dar un paseillo por el
downtown on the motorcycle Luis Miguel is not
centro con la moto Luis Miguel no está
here no
aquí no
tesa
tesa
Luis Miguel I haven't seen him who
Luis Miguel no lo he visto yo a
So we went for a walk
quién Entonces nos fuimos a dar un paseo
on the motorcycle Look mar Lucas mar Lucas
con la moto Mira mar Lucas mar Lucas la
we saw her the other day
vimos el otro día
Look look mar Lucas This is a girl who
Mira mira mar Lucas Esta es una chica
Cher influencer and singer okay we
que Cher influencer y cantante vale
went downtown on the motorcycle I say let's
fuimos por el centro con la moto Digo
gossip to see what we see no and
vamos aí a cotill a ver qué vemos no y
here we stop at the z because
aquí nos paramos en la z porque se
Someone was coming down the stairs
estaba bajando alguien por las escaleras
and there were all the
y estaba toda la
people and here to see who it was and it was Malca
gente y aquí a ver quién era y era malca
who is a girl who
que es una chica que
well she is the one from naa rech there in
bueno pues es la de naa rech allí en
chavalería we have talked a lot about
chavalería hemos hablado mucho de
her I have her songs too I don't
ella yo tengo sus canciones también no
dislike her
me disgustan sus
songs And well there I am standing
canciones Y bueno pues ahí estoy parado
look here I come out okay look this is an
mira aquí salgo vale mira esta es una
Instagram story of
historia de Instagram de
[Music]
[Música]
her where am I I am standing here with
ella dónde estoy estoy aquí parado con
the
la
motorcycle where am I I don't see it Ah look look
moto dónde estoy no lo veo Ah mira mira
here I am with the motorcycle look here I am
aquí estoy con la moto mira aquí estoy
with the motorcycle there
con la moto ahí
for who esp let's see if he takes off his ilenia
par qui esp a ver si se quita la ilenia
and you see it let's see if he takes off his ilenia and you see
y lo veis a ver si se quita la ilenia y
it
lo
Here I am with the motorcycle here I am
veis Aquí estoy con la moto aquí estoy
standing with the motorcycle you can see the two
parado con la moto lo veis los dos
helmets We saw who I saw
cascos Vimos a quién vi
Javi
Javi
[Music]
[Música]
ah bizarre [
ah bizarra
bizarre
bizarra
[Music]
[Música]
for a
por una
photo this one if I'm not mistaken was Carlos
foto este si no me equivoco era Carlos
baut Ah You go down Sevilla street you go
baut Ah Tú vas por la calle de Sevilla
seeing you go down Sevilla street you
viendo vas por la calle de Sevilla te
[Music]
[Música]
finding a corridor a little bit of
encontrando pasillo un poquito de
corridor Oh Carl is spectacular
pasillo Oh Carl está espectacular
[Music]
[Música]
eh Uncle Carlos ba looks spectacular at
eh Tío Carlos ba está espectacular con
50 years old
50 años
[Music]
[Música]
eh
eh
And well I saw a lot of people I mean I've
Y bueno pues vi mucha gente O sea he
seen a lot of people that I haven't been
visto mucha gente que no que no le he
able to ask for photos or anything eh man I saw
podido pedir fotos ni nada eh tío vi
Alejandro
Alejandro
San I saw Alejandro San man in all my
San vi Alejandro San tío en todo mi
face in all my face
careto en todo mi careto
man I sat down
tío me senté
eh well we were over there the two of us
Eh bueno estábamos por allí los dos en
like papari not to see what we hunted on
plan papari no a ver qué cazábamos el
Monday
lunes
and I said to Enrique let's sit
y le digo al Enrique vamos a sentarnos
here quietly we're here having
aquí tranquilamente estamos aquí tomando
a coffee in the Hall of in the Hall of
un café en el Hall de en el Hall del del
Alfonso 13 we started looking around at the
Alfonso 13 nos pusimos a ver por ahí las
exhibitions I don't know what we sat in
exposiciones no sé qué nos sentamos en
the Hall just us in the Hall okay
el Hall nosotros solos en el Hall vale
just us in the Hall
nosotros solos en el Hall
and grab
y coge
[Music]
[Música]
and And this guy comes over there
y Y viene uno un taru ahí
super strong and sits next to
superfuerte y se sienta al lado
me he sits like this next to me and I say well you've
mía se sienta así al lado mía y digo
sat Cotilla here too
pues has sentado aquí a Cotilla también
or whatever and suddenly I see him
o lo que sea y de repente veo que
appear coming out of the hallway no that he
aparece saliendo del pasillo no que
came from his room or whatever
vendría de su habitación o lo que sea
with four gorillas around Alejandro
con cuatro gorilas alrededor Alejandro
San I
San me quedé
froze I stayed with Maybe  if I had
congelados me quedé con A lo mejor si le
told Alejandro for a picture or
llego a decir Alejandro una foto una o
something the man would stop but of course
algo se para el hombre pero claro es que
I froze the only thing that came out
me quedé congelado lo único que me salió
was Enrique Look Enrique Look dude
fue Enrique Mira Enrique Mira tío
Alejandro San Alejandro San
Alejandro San Alejandro San
kid Alejandro San kid and he went
chaval Alejandro San chaval y pasó por
all over my face eh one of the
toda mi cara eh coge así uno de los
gorillas grabs this like this boom and stands up in front of me
gorilas pum y se pone de pie delante mía
just in case I was getting up or something
por si acaso yo me iba levantado o algo
and and and nothing and he
y
went through here by my face by
y nada y pasó por aquí por mi cara por
my face there I could touch him Look
mi cara ahí lo podía tocar Mira por mi
Alejandro went through my face dude Maybe I
cara pasó Alejandro s tío A lo mejor le
would have asked him for a picture and he stops the
hubiera pedido una foto y se para al
man Maybe I would have asked him for a
hombre A lo mejor le hubiera pedido una
picture I'm never going to get that chance
foto Ya esa oportunidad no la voy a
again in my life
tener más en la vida
eh but the thing is that I stayed like this dude it's that I
eh pero es que me quedé así tío es que
stayed I'm just that Alejandro is all over
me quedé Yo es que Alejandro se en todda
my face dude all over my
mi cara tío en toda mi
face and nothing What else What else did I see who else have I
cara y nada Qué más Qué más vi a quién
seen that hasn't asked for a
más he visto que no haya pedido
photo let's
foto
see tiktoker of these I've seen a
a ver tiktoker de estas he visto un
lot I've seen marluca LoL Lolita I
montón he visto a marluca LoL la Lolita
also saw her on the
la vi también por la
[Music]
[Música]
street who else did I see Javi Raquel boyo I
calle a quién más vi Javi a Raquel boyo
saw her yesterday or the day before yesterday  Raquel boyo I
La vi ayer o antes de ayer a Raquel boyo
saw her yesterday or the day before
La vi ayer o antes
yesterday to see H echoist to the video and
ayer a ver H echoist al vídeo y
[Music]
[Música]
I remember
recuerdo
this the Alfonso
este el Alfonso
13 we are there having a drink
13 estamos ahí tomando
something good family here we are
algo bueno familia aquí estamos
trying to go unnoticed
intentando pasar desapercibidos
pretending like what we are the
haciéndonos como los que somos los
kids we are sitting in good this what
chavalines estamos sentados en buen esto
would this be For me it is embarrassing a
qu sería Esto para mí es vergüenza una
reception like some kind of external in
recepi como una especie de externo en
the
los
gardens and the truth is that we are
jardines y la verdad que estamos eso
trying to act like we are a couple
intentando hacer como que somos un par
of foreigners who have come Who is
de de guiris que hemos venido Quién es
the Messenger of gods hair today
el Messenger de diosos el pelo hoy más
lighter while he doesn't speak his mouth I don't
claro mientras que no habla la boca no
know if you can for foreigner And who is the
sé si pued por guiri Y quién es el
Messenger of Messenger But anyway Here we are
Messenger del Messenger Pero bueno Aquí
going to spend the afternoon let's see
vamos a echar la tardecita vamos a ver
who we see So this pending give it a
quién vemos Así que estlo pendiente dle
like we are in Seville capital
like nos encontramos en Sevilla capital
and it is that the Latin Grammy awards are going to be held
y es que se va a celebrar los premios
and we are arriving at the
Latin gramy y estamos llegando al hotel
Alfonso 13 hotel we have it there in the background and
Alfonso 13 lo tenemos allí al fondo y
apparently they have told me that
por lo visto me han chivado que allí
none other than Rosalía is
está nada más y nada menos que Rosalía
staying there and
hospedada y en
soon we are going to see
breve vamos a ver a
Shakira man Shakira nobody has seen her
Shakira tío Shakira no la ha visto nadie
eh I mean Shakira  he got from one car to
eh o sea Shakira se montó de un coche a
another and no one has seen him on the street
otro y no lo ha visto nadie por la calle
all week they've been
durante todas las semana se han estado
seeing all the famous people more or less
viendo todos los famosos más o menos
but Shakira no one has seen her I
pero Shakira no la ha visto nadie yo
think she's gone to a hotel dude
creo que se ha metido en un hotel tío
Paula Echevarría is here today dude Paula Echevarría is here dude Paula
está aquí Paula Echevarría ha venido hoy
Echevarría
tío está aquí Paula Echevarría
dude uh she's here Paula Echebarría
tío está aquí Paula echebarría
dude
tío
uh she's here Paula eb barría
eh está aquí Paula eb barría
dude but of course anyone can
tío pero claro cualquiera la
see her it's because I just found out a little
ve es que me me acabo de enterar hace un
while ago I just found out a little while ago it's because I've been
rato me acabo de enterar hace un rato es
I've been up all late well all
que he estado Yo to tarde bueno toda
afternoon I had an important meeting this
tarde Tenía una reunión importante esta
afternoon and I went to see
tarde y he ido a ver
Ari Dallas's sister who is
a a Ari a la hermana de Dallas que sí
going yes she's going to the gala Arian is going to the
que va sí que va a la gala arian va a la
gala she called me in the morning her
gala me llamó por la mañana me llamó la
mother called me come on let's go eat I don't know I don't
madre vente que vamos a comer no sé no
know how much and I was asleep because I
sé cuánto y yo estaba dormido porque me
woke up What are you saying ca for God's sake torr
desperté Qué dices ca por Dios torr
Sevilla are you going to compare him to Alfonso
Sevilla lo vas a comparar con el Alfonso
's
de
daughter run Javi run towards her but
hija corre Javi corre hacia ella pero si
yes I don't know where she is I mean yes I know which
es que no sé dónde está O sea sí sé cuál
hotel she is but I don't know
es el hotel en donde está pero no sé a
what time will I be able to see her come in or whatever I mean I do
qué hora la podré ver entrar o lo que
n't know family I think we're going to
sea o sea no sé familia creo que vamos a
charge the phone I think we're going to charge the
cargar el móvil creo que vamos a cargar
phone go see Paula I would go but I
el móvil ve a ver a Paula iría pero es
see it very complicated man I would go I do
que lo veo muy complicado tío iría iría
n't care there but I see it very
no me importa ahí pero es que lo veo muy
complicated man
complicado tío
Because at what time do I I mean if now are
Porque a qué hora voy o sea si ahora son
the gramis then when the gramis end
los gramis luego terminen los gramis
these people have parties and things
esta gente tienen fiestas y cosas
man I mean it's completely impossible
tío o sea es es completamente imposible
man it's completely impossible to
tío es completamente imposible
know what's going on man does it tell you my daughter
saber qué va hombre te sa a mía hija mía
what Alfonso
lo que es el Alfonso
13 is You were with Dallas's family Yes
13 Estuviste con la familia de Dallas Sí
yes I was with the mother and with the sister
sí estuve con la madre y con la hermana
there in her hotel let's go she called me to go
ahí en su hotel vamos me llamó para que
eat but I was asleep What
fueran a comer pero estaba yo dormido Lo
happens is that we haven't seen each other for a
que pasa que nos hemos visto nada un
while half an hour we saw each other because
rato media hora nos hemos visto porque
I had an important date at 6
yo tenía una cita a las 6 importante
and and she well be there she be
y y ya ella pues estar allí ella estar
there let's see I'll see if she has uploaded any
allí a ver voy a ver si ha sube alguna
story she be there at the at the
historia ella estar allí en la en la
gala she is going to the gala they have
gala ella va para la gala la la han
invited her eh As an artist eh look at the V
invitado eh Como artista eh mira lo V
hit eh look look at her Look at her look at
pelotazo eh mira mírala
her But  let's go on the red carpet eh
mírala Pero vamos en la alfombra roja eh
the
la
colleague and nothing
colega y nada
e Tomorrow she leaves early tomorrow she leaves
e Mañana se va temprano mañana se va
early that's why we won't see each other anymore I
temprano por eso no nos vemos más yo
wanted her to come so we could do
quería que viniera para que hiciéramos
a live show and
un directo y
such a
tal
great idea Carlos very good idea
muy buena idea carlas muy buena idea
Carlos very good idea no because look
carlas muy buena idea no porque mira
because I know that
porque yo sé que
later they have a party then Of course yes they have a
luego tienen una fiesta entonces Claro
party How do you know, I mean
si tienen una fiesta Cómo sabes tú o sea
if you tell me, well look At 1 in
si a mí me dices tú pues mira A la 1 de
the morning more or less the
la mañana más o menos se termina la
party ends and everyone goes to their hotel
fiesta y cada uno se va para su hotel
Hey, I wouldn't mind taking a moment
Oye pues no me importaría un momento
eh to ask for a photo but of course I do
eh para pedirle una foto pero claro es
n't know, I mean everyone will leave the
que no sé o sea cada uno se irá de la
party at their own time I can't
fiesta a la hora que le da la gana no me
imagine I say let's
imagino digo yo
go and it's that according to what they've told me she'll
vamos y es que según me han comentado
be here around 7 in the afternoon
sobre las 7 de la tarde estaría aquí
okay I can see some fellow
vale Ya veo algunos compañeros
reporters and well let's see if we
reporteros y bueno vamos a ver si
can see Shakira Well I'm already at
podemos ver a Shakira Bueno ya estoy en
the entrance I just got here and let's see if
la entrada Acabo de llegar y a ver si
Rosalía comes out by chance she's
Rosalía saliera por casualidad
not cool yet eh I don't know if I'll be able to
no est reolín todavía eh No sé si vo a
last long This is the
aguantar mucho tiempo Este es el hotel
Alfonso 3 hotel in Seville okay where they're staying
Alfonso 3 Sevilla vale donde se hospedan
most of the famous singers
la mayoría de los famosos cantantes
guest presenters at
presentadores invitados de la gala de
this year's gramis gala okay here in
los gramis de este año vale aquí en
Seville almost the hotel okay look at it the
Sevilla casin el hotel vale miradlo el
hotel is crazy
hotel es
crazy the pajamas they
casada una locura una locura el pijamita
give you to get comfortable
que te dan para que te ponga tú cómodo
at
por la
night Carlos vive we saw him twice the
noche Carlos vive lo vimos dos veces el
super
tío super
close guy eh the super close guy Carlos vive
cercano eh el tío super cercano Carlos
e First I
e Primero me lo
ran into him First I ran into Carlos
encontré Primero me lo encontré a Carlos
vivel when I arrived in the afternoon I'm
vivel cuando llegué por la tarde voy
walking down Alfonso
andando por ahí por la calle del Alfonso
3 street and I run into him Carl What's up man I
3 y me lo encuentro Carl Qué pasa hombre
don't know what And I didn't ask for a photo or anything I posted
no sé qué Y no le pedí foto ni nada puse
a tweet and I said wow Enrique dude Well
un tweet y digo [__] Enrique tío Pues
no I've been with Carlos vivel and I didn't
no que he estado con Carlos vive y no le
ask for a photo or anything [ __ ]'
pedido foto ni nada [__] tío
influencer dude I don't know what I don't know how much And
influencer no sé qué no sé cuánto Y
then I took it and when we saw him the
entonces cogí y cuando lo vimos la
second time This was more or
segunda vez Esto fue más o
less I think this was 5 minutes
menos yo creo que esto fue 5 minutos
after see Alejandro
después de ve Alejandro
San that trust you is that Alejandro San
San que fíate tú es que Alejandro San
surely if we had said something to him
seguramente si le hubiéramos dicho algo
the man takes a photo
el hombre se hace una foto
too
también
for sure well for all my people from info
seguro bueno para toda mi gente de info
influencers this nothing a hug
influencers este nada un abrazo Los
We love you and how good that we are here in
queremos y qué bueno que estemos aquí en
Seville for the gramis maximum  Thanks
Sevilla para los gramis máximo Gracias
for all the Carlos vive It's not just
por todos los Carlos vive No es
anyone man Of course
cualquiera hombre Por supuesto que
man Carlos
hombre Carlos
vive Carlos
vive Carlos
[Music]
[Música]
vive to the artists to the music to the art
viveo a los artistas a la música al arte
to the joy no Gabi I don't take off my
a la alegría no Gabi no me quito la
cap because I had very bad hair Gabi I
gorra porque tenía muy malos pelos Gabi
put my cap on now before
me he puesto la gorra ahora antes de
starting the live because I saw myself
empezar el directo porque me he visto
like bad hair and I said pum
como malos pelos y he dicho pum
cap to the exit then I wash my head
gorra al sal luego me lavo la cabeza
out that [ __ ] disgusting ass just
fuera esa [__] asquerosidad culo acaba
happened more disgusting
de pasar más asqueroso
they are diverting the
están desviando el
topic
tema
great tremendous
genial tremendo
eh tremendous eh tremendous Carlos
eh tremendo eh tremendo Carlos
vive my partner Javi Oliveira okay
vive mi compañero Javi oliveira vale
follow him telesalseo also there
seguirlo telesalseo también ahí
you will find all the gossip So
encontraréis todos los chismecitos Así
my people from info influencer we are going to
que mi gente de info influencer vamos a
go to an event while we are going to try to
ir a un evento mientras vamos a intentar
record something there because because he has
grabar allí algo porque porque él se ha
met Carlos vive he has caught her he has
encontrado con Carlos vive la ha pillado
caught her by egg that she was there the
la ha pillado a huevo que estaba allí lo
norm and nothing The vive the typical ones you
norm y nada Los vive los típicos te
run into Carlos vive man Seville is
cruzas con Carlos vive tío Sevilla es
crazy right now man I mean you
una locura ahora mismo tío o sea te
run into Carlos vive on the street
cruzas con Carlos vive por la calle
right now let's go You are walking down the
ahora mismo vamos Estás andando por la
street and you run into Carlos vive well
calle y te cruzas con Carlos vive pues
that's it  so nothing Now we're going to a
eso sí así que nada Ahora vamos a un
flamenco photocall according to what they've told me
fotocol de flamenco según me han dicho
Okay, well anyone can be there
Vale pues puede estar pues cualquiera de
of all those who are here today well who
de todos los que están aquí hoy pues que
want to go there they've told me that
quieran ir allí que me han dicho que
anyone can go we're going to
pueden ir cualquiera nos vamos a
So there we go We're going to go over and
Así que va Nos vamos a acercar y vamos a
see if we can record something from the photocall
ver si podemos grabar algo del fotocol
like this Okay let's see if we can catch something
así Bueno a ver si podemos pillar Algo
we're going to Plaza España family
vamos para la plaza España familia
talking to Shakira let's go see Shakira
hablando con Shakira vamos a ver Shakira
now watch out Shakira Shakira Shakira it's
ahora ojo Shakira Shakira Shakira eres
you Wow we're talking to the snitches
tú Wow estamos hablando con los chivatos
and we're going to try to meet up with Shakira
y vamos a intentar reunirnos con Shakira
when I find Shakira I'm going to
cuando me encuentre a Shakira le voy a
do the same thing to her as I did to Carlos Vi are you going to
hacer lo mismo que a Carlos vi vas a
ask about Piqué I don't think so
preguntar por Piqué No creo no
No man I'm going to ask him about the
No hombre que le voy a preguntar por lo
big thing he's given us
gran nos ha dado
an agreement with Casio the Kings League has
un acuerdo con Casio la Kings League ha
reached an agreement with Casio who
llegado a un acuerdo con Casio que
asks about Piqué no Well both things
pregunta por piqu no Bueno las dos cosas
are fine well let's see if we see Shakira we're
está bien bueno a ver si vemos a Shakira
going to ask her well I'm not going to
le vamos a preguntar bueno no le voy a
ask her anything I'm going to do the same as
preguntar nada voy a hacer lo mismo de
with Carlos Vi I'm going to say hello how are you
con Carlos vive le voy a decir hola qué
And ask me for a photo of her if she
tal Y que me pida una foto de ella si
wants it's the logical thing to do it's the
quiere es lo lógico es lo
logical thing  There are many artists that I saw
lógico hay muchos artistas que los vi
like this,
así
eh, they drive their car up to
eh que pegan el coche pegan el coche a
the entrance of the hotel and go
la entrada del hotel y entran
straight in, let's go, they jump from the car to the
directamente vamos saltan del coche a la
room. And there are many that I've seen
habitación Y hay muchos que los he visto
like this and I don't know who they are,
así y no sé quiénes son la
honestly. Well, family, we are
verdad Bueno familia nos encontramos
right now in the Plaza de España in
ahora mismo en la plaza de España de
Seville where. Well, here there were a lot
Sevilla donde Bueno aquí había un montón
of famous people that I didn't talk to, man, I
de famosos a los que no le hablé tío o
mean, here there are a lot of famous people that I did
sea aquí hay un montón de famosos a los
n't talk to because between not
que no le hablé porque entre que no
having a voice and them talking as much as
tenía voz y que estaban hablando lo que
I could.
se me daba cosa va a tener lugar dentro
The Universal Flamenco Gala is going to take place in a few minutes.
de unos minutos la gala Universal del
Okay, we have a lot
flamenco vale tenemos por aquí un montón
of familiar faces around here, here via Raquel
de caras conocidas aquí aquí via Raquel
Boyos yesterday. Well, we can't
boyos ayer Pues bueno pues no podemos
get in because we can't jump over the
pasar porque no nos podemos salta la
fence, no, but obviously now. I'll
valla no pero evidentemente ahora Lo
try. Now that I'm losing
intentaré yo ahora que estoy perdiendo
weight, maybe I can get in through the bars.
peso lo mismo por ahí entre los barrotes
Let's take a walk.
me puedo meter vamos a dar una vuel cita
Look, over here, look, there's María del Monte. Come on, I
por aquí mira ahí está María del monte
want to ask her
ven que le quiero preguntar una
something. She's taking a selfie. María
cosa que se está haciendo un selfi María
del Monte. I'm hallucinating. María del Monte. What's
del monte yo que alucino María del
María del
monte que se está haciendo María del
Monte taking? María José, selfie. María del Monte.
Monte María José selfi María del monte
Look.  get up you can't I'm sitting I
mira levántate no se puede estoy sentada
promise you I'm not sitting I
os prometo que no estoy sentada que
'm up
estoy levantada
ig to eat uncomfortable to look at her
ig para comér incómoda para mirarla
Okay, well,
Bueno
Bertigo V's daughter you
vamos bueno la hija de bertigo V me
told me in the comments that she was this
dijiste en los comentarios que era esta
woman this
mujer esta
girl how is she how are you are
muchacha cómo está cómo está estás
happy man of course I'm stepping
contenta hombre por supuesto yo me hecho
to the
al
side they robbed me of those things not to talk we
lado robaron de esas cosas me no hablar
came to talk about other things Hey why don't you
venimos a hablar de otras Oye por qué no
ever want to talk about being robbed I
quiere hablar nunca de que le robaron O
mean I don't understand I said Maria What's
sea no lo entiendo le dije María Qué
up How are you after you were
pasa Cómo estás después de que te
robbed the other day I don't know what And he says a
robaron el otro día no sé qué Y dice tos
serious cough I don't want to talk about those things Better
seria esas cosas no quiero hablar Mejor
we talk about other things What's up I mean it's not like it was
hablamos de otras cosas Qué pasa o sea
your fault that
que ni que tú tuvieras la culpa de que
you were
te
robbed I mean it doesn't matter no Well look we're having a
roben O sea no importa no Pues mira lo
bad time I don't know what I don't understand
pasemos mal no sé qué No entiendo por
why not I mean I don't understand why it
qué no O sea no entiendo por qué le
bothered him that I asked him that event and
molestaba que le preguntaba eso evento y
the event event How are you doing Well I'm
el evento evento Cómo te lo está pasando
going to be able to go to a few events
Pues voy a poder ir a pocos eventos
because I have work stuff but as soon as I
porque tengo cosas de trabajo pero a lo
can I'll be there here I am look you
que pueda ahí estaré aquí estoy mira
know what's going on the microphone was
sabes qué pasa que el micrófono estaba
off dude and the audio is being recorded
apagado tío y se está grabando el audio
with the sound of the cell phone  I put the
con el sonido del móvil puse el
microphone on but I didn't turn it on man could you
micrófono pero no lo encendí tío podid
talk to isap after your wedding come on bye bye
hablar con isap después de su boda venga
my soul
hasta lueguito hasta luego mi alma
many
Muchas
[Music]
[Música]
thanks Well very well here to enjoy
gracias Pues muy bien aquí a disfrutar a
enjoy a lot with your friends and
disfrutar mucho de los compañeros y a
spend have a
pasar a pasar un rato
magnificent time Listen to the greatest thing
magnífico Escuchar lo más grande que hay
in the world which is
en el mundo que es el
flamenco let's see how everyone
flamenco vamos a ver como todo el mundo
comes very handsome very gala it's almost
viene bien guapete bien de gala es casi
universal week is taking place
semana universal está teniendo lugar
here I didn't say anything to him It's almost man Seville
aquí no le dije nada Es casi tío Sevilla
the gramis something historic something brutal
los gramis algo histórico algo brutal
that the
que ha conseguido la
city has achieved and if everything happens according to conditions and there are no
ciudad y si pas todo en condiciones y no
altercations then surely
hay ningún altercado pues seguramente
more great things will come for Luis
vendrán más cosas grandes para Luis
well how do you feel
buena cómo te siente
queando what a great event what a
queando pedazo de evento pedazo de
week sees the microphone off man
semana lo ve el micrófono apagado
I'm the worst eh As to dedicate myself to
tío Soy el peor eh Como para dedicarme a
this
esto
eh captain
eh capit
give it
dealo
well
bien
delighted I saw for the first time with
encantadísimo vi por primera vez con
Rivera that we were there that he was sick
Rivera que estábamos allí que estaba mal
in the hospital in Seville do you
en el hospital en Sevilla te
remember I couldn't talk to you Later
acuerdas no pude hablar contigo Ya luego
and we will record you for a while listen to me the
y te grabamos un ratito escúchame el
event how is it it's wonderful because it is
evento qué tal es una maravilla porque
the first time in history that
que es la primera vez en la historia se
the gramis that come out of America are held in Seville
haga en Sevilla los gramis que salgan de
come here well you have to be
América se venga aquí pues hay que estar
o very happy very happy that it is in my
oa muy contento muy feliz que sea en mi
city Hey laa
ciud Oye laa
such had a great time I was that
tal se lo pasaron muy bien Yo estaba ese
day at Joana Jiménez's who got married
día en la de Joana Jiménez que se casó
the same day in another part of Seville So I
el mismo día en otra parte de Sevilla O
was also there
sea que que también estuve de Muchas
Thank you very much We are from YouTube
gracias Nosotros somos de YouTube
Enrique García and Javi Oliveira
Enrique García y Javi oliveira
telesalseo telesalseo
telesalseo telesalseo
Lu good no Oh what a shame this interview
Lu buenas no Ay qué pena esta entrevista
What a shame the interview p Vega man that
Qué pena la entrevista p Vega tío que no
the microphone can't be heard man What a shame eh
se escuche el micrófono tío Qué pena eh
spectacular
espectacular
how do you feel in this week of the
cómo te sientes en esta semana de los
gramis here in
gramis aquí en
Seville I would
Sevilla yo
say How beautiful
diría Qué guapa
eh wonderful spectacular I got
eh maravilloso espectacular me
excited gua gu at once now Soler what have I said wh
emocionado gua gu ot vez ahora Soler qu
said what have I said p
he dicho qu dicho qué he dicho p
Vega better that I lose my voice again
Vega mejor que me quede sin voz otra vez
no how are you doing
no qué tal to
that you have caught me here la toñi la
que me habéis cogido aquí la toñi la
toñi this what salseo Enrique García and
toñi esto qué salseo Enrique García y
teles salseo Andalusian Sevillian 100%
teles salseo andaluces sevillano 100%
this what salseo says la toñi Enrique
esto que salseo dice la toñi Enrique
García and telesalseo Andalusian Sevillian
García y telesalseo andaluces sevillano
100% ask a question that makes
100% hacer alguna pregunta que tenga
sense please ask a question that makes
sentido por favor hacer alguna pregunta
sense  please I don't know the
que tenga sentido por favor No sé la
truth we could have asked
verdad que le podíamos haber preguntado
Toñi what question did you think would have made
a toñi qué qué pregunta creía ustedes
sense
sentido
what
qué
question what question could we have asked
pregunta qué pregunta le podríamos haber
Toñi says ask me a question
hecho a toñi dice hacerme una pregunta
that makes sense please I don't know what you
que tenga sentido por favor No sé lo que
would have asked her to make her say that
le habrían preguntado para que dijera
Javi it's your turn
eso Javi te toca
the gala hasn't started it hasn't started it's
nada la gala no ha empezado ha empezado
not started I'm going to go in now the
no ha empezado voy a entrar ahora la
gala has started on TV how are we doing on
gala ha empezado en la tele cómo vamos
TV we're doing Scandal
la tele vamos de Escándalo
great I'm very happy
estupendamente estoy muy contenta adó
come on see later thanks we asked her
venga Hasta luego graas le preguntamos
Well family Marina wouldn't have missed a single
Bueno familia a Marina no se le hubiera
one of course daughter but Marina
ido ni uno claro hija pero es que Marina
is a professional in that that's her thing
es una profesional en eso es lo suyo
Marina is that that's her thing who am I
Marina es que es lo
Well I make
suyo yo quién soy Pues yo hago aquí
videos and live shows each one has their thing Let's
vídeos y directos cada uno Tiene lo
see how they go let's
suyo A ver vamos a ver cómo van
not see how they
no vamos a ver cómo
go Latin
van latin
Premier
Premier alfombra
red carpet let's see I think I think we have
roja a ver Creo que creo que tenemos por
[Music]
[Música]
here Thank you guys Thank you very much I
aquí Gracias chicos Muchísimas gracias O
mean don't worry you're
sea tú no te preocupes te estás
literally carrying this on your own I mean do
carreando esto tú sola literal O sea que
n't pay us let them pay you hey hey hey we
no nos paguen que te paguen oye oye oye
have we have we have a
que tenemos que tenemos que tenemos a
pasadilla
pasadilla
madill pasadilla it's true it's true I
madill es verdad es verdad
saw
vi [__]
damn asked Ask her to
pregun Pregúntale
pass the earpiece the earpiece
a que pase pinganillo el pinganillo
padill okay okay Wait for it to come
padill vale vale Espérate que venga
wait okay okay okay I saw
espérate vale vale vale que yo vi
one for her that comes out talking well anyway it's coming it's coming it's
un por ella que sale hablando bueno en
coming guys you you
fin ya viene ya viene viene chicos tú tú
ask I put it on I put the helmet on no you
pregunt le pongo le pongo el casco no tú
put the helmet on and have Spock
le pones el casco y que spock le
ask her there it is please it's like
pregunte ahí está por favor es como
fulfilling one of the biggest dreams of my
cumplir uno de los mayores sueños de mi
life man wait a moment guys eh I'm going
vida tío espera un momento chicos eh voy
to talk to her a little bit first Hi
a hablar un poquito antes con ella Hola
Paz How are you how is she pretty Hey How
Paz Qué tal cómo está bonita Oye Qué
pretty she's wearing green like Andalusia you don't
guapa viene de verde como Andalucía no
know I'm seeing a lot of glamour already tell
sabes que estoy viendo mucho glamour ya
you she turns around I'm seeing
te lo ella se da la vuelta estoy viendo
super glamour they're so shiny and I feel a a
super glamour son mucho brillo y siento
joy and a pride of my
una una una alegría y un orgullo de mi
land Because Andalusia is happy it
tierra Porque es que Andalucía es alegre
always wears its eyes with the
siempre lleva los ojos también con el
green too it's very pretty I love it Look
verdecito está muy guapa Me encanta Mira
we want to sing She wants to sing I'll
estamos que quiere cantar Quiere cantar
sing cone if you want whatever you
yo canto cono si tú quieres lo que tú
want but how beautiful that this is
quieras pero qué bonito que esto se
celebrated Here it's very beautiful especially
celebra Aquí es muy bonito sobre todo
because of the change of culture for the union
por el cambio de cultura por la unión
this is beautiful we open the cigarettes to the
esto es precioso abrimos los fasos al
world man please And also it's that
mundo hombre por favor Y además es que
Andalusia is also a land of art
Andalucía es tierra también de de arte
No, I have thought about it, I say whatever happens, they are
No yo lo he pensado digo como venga se
going to fall in love, they are going to fall in love and they are not
van a enamorar se van a enamorar y no
going to stop doing the Latin
van a dejar de hacer aquí los Latin
Grammys here, more than one will ever stay here to
gramy nunca más de uno se queda aquí a
live safely, dun, what is
vivir segur dun me lo qu
left, I tell you, it seems complicated and
queda te digo me parece complicado y
you give it hard, big, this with
vosotr darle duro grande esta con
losing
perd
said nothing, I will give myself an award there at the
dich nada yo me dar un premio ahí en la
Premier very well Congratulations,
Premier muy bien Enhorabuena muchas
thank you very much, you know Look Carl is alive Look Carl lives
graci sab Mira Carl vive Mira Carl vive
here again Natalia
aquí otra vez Natalia
Natalia
Natalia
c climbed a [ __ ] really impressive
c escal una [__] enci impresionante
first it seems like she is at the fair and
primero parece que está en la feria y
second she almost trips what
segundo casi se tropieza elde que ha
happened imagine Natalia sailor face with
pasado imate Natalia marinera cara con
hands hugging person with hand
manos abrazando persona con la mano
raised face in love I have to take
levantada cara enamorada tengo que hacer
a curious trip eh p On Monday, Monday I'm
un viaje curioso eh p El lunes el lunes
not going on Sunday I have to travel, let
no me voy el domingo tengo que recorrer
's go, I have to travel half the peninsula, not half the
vamos tengo que recorrer media No media
entire Peninsula, the
península la Península entera la
entire Peninsula Pau but thank you very much
Península entera Pau pero muchas gracias
Thank you very much for your collaboration,
Muchísimas gracias por tu colaboración
daughter, let's
hija
see what
a ver qué
comes out,
sale
who else do we see
a quién más
that I turned to look at you and said how could they
vemos que te volteé a mirar y dije cómo
not take me to be interviewed,
no me van a llevar a que me entreviste
name of Andalusia, well, name in the name
nom de Andalucía bueno nombre en nombre
of  Twitch because we're live and
de Twitch porque estamos en directo y
look I have something for you to communicate
mira tengo unco para que te comuniques
Yes yes this Emptying me for Ah There it is, there it is
Sí sí esto Vaciando yo por Ah Ya
Someone wants revenge and our
está Alguien quiere vengarse y nuestros
names are on the table But why
nombres están en la mesa Pero por qué
we were a joke could it be what
nosotros fera coña puede ser lo que haya
happened with the absolute elra is coming now I
pasado con el elra absoluto viene ahora
saw Ah comes Puerto Rico cl
vi Ah viene Puerto Rico cl
playing Hey Arrebato hasn't been there, no
jugando Oye el Arrebato no ha estado no
reason to be because the man
porque estar porque el hombre por lo
apparently knows the rep, I would ask him plush he
visto conoce el rep le preguntaría felpa
has enar arato what plush does
tiene enar arato cuá felpa tiene
Arrebato have in his house throwing a towel a
Arrebato en su casa echándose un toal un
person c a person c
persona c un persona c
Royal is playing a WWE online Hey are
Royal se está echando un WWE online Oye
we getting closer or what are we getting closer or
nos acercamos o qué nos acercamos o
what c or what Yes Ana Yes yes Ana my daughter
qué c o qué Sí Ana Sí sí Ana hija mía
yes 900 km more or less Well I don't know well
sí 900 km más o menos Pues no lo sé pues
no more I think
no yo creo que
more I think more Thank you very much
más yo creo que más Muchas gracias
Charlie well we'll see what
Charlie bueno veremos a ver qué es lo
comes out not what it has to be that it's
que sale no lo que tenga que ser que sea
something else we can't do
otra cosa no podemos hacer